<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Curve Counting on Sjoerd Beentjes</title>
    <link>https://SjoerdVBeentjes.github.io/tags/curve-counting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Curve Counting on Sjoerd Beentjes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Sjoerd Beentjes</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/curve-counting/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Crepant resolution conjecture for Donaldson-Thomas invariants</title>
      <link>https://SjoerdVBeentjes.github.io/project/crc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SjoerdVBeentjes.github.io/project/crc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The crepant resolution conjecture for Donaldson-Thomas invariants is a statement about the enumerative geometry of two related geometries. It relates the Donaldson-Thomas generating series of a certain type of threedimensional Calabi-Yau orbifold $\mathcal{X}$ to that of a particular crepant resolution $Y$ of its coarse moduli space $X$.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a nice &lt;a href=&#34;https://SjoerdVBeentjes.github.io/files/PosterBrAG.pdf&#34;/&gt;poster&lt;/a&gt;
 I made about this conjecture for the British Algebraic Geometry (BrAG) conference held in Cambridge, from 11 to 13 September 2017. It contains two results:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The example shows that analytic continuation of the generating series is required for the conjecture to hold. This seems to be a new phenomenon in the DT-world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have proven a nice formula in a motivic Hall algebra relating the Hilbert scheme of curves on the resolution to the Hilbert scheme of curves on the orbifold.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the moment, &lt;a href=&#34;https://folk.uio.no/jorgeren/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Jørgen Rennemo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://math.rice.edu/~jrc9/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;John Calabrese&lt;/a&gt; and I have joined forces to complete the proof of the conjecture. It turns out the underlying statement is an equality of rational functions, after a change of variables. The conjecture follows by expanding this rational function about different points. This requires some clever use of wallcrossing in the Hall algebra.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
